Ebichu Oshi Culture: Perpetration Activities Vol. 1
Can you oshi? The Oshi-ing of the Oshi
Good afternoon
Hello everyone!
Welcome to the Chayama Tone Festival 2024 stage event!
We, Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku, attendance number 13, Sakurai Ogura and
Attendance number 14, Yuno Kokubo and
And attendance number 15, Nonoka Kazami.
Pleased to meet you.
And we will be conducting this event.
The live performer is Yamanaka Ko.
Please remember the announcer is Yamanaka.
This is MBS announcer Makoto Yamanaka.
Please give my best regards.
Pleased to meet you.
You're Yamanaka, right?
Mr. Yamanaka.
I was told this is the house.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
The Ebituaries...
I'm sure you've seen the various faces we've been working with today.
How was the atmosphere?
It was really crowded, and there were gourmet foods and goods stores.
It was a lot of fun to see so many different things.
And the three of you are also the main MCs for the "Guess Culture" program that airs once a month on MBS late at night on Tuesdays.
They also appear as the main MCs on our TV show, "Push Culture," which airs on MBS once a month on Tuesdays at midnight.
Please tell us about the highlights of the show.
This program introduces the various aspects of each of us.
It has only been aired twice, but it will continue to be aired in the future, so I hope you will watch it as many times as possible.
What is the atmosphere like with Mr. Iwai and Ms. Kano?
It's the first time I've had the pleasure of working with them, but they're really kind and they knows a lot about anime.
I'm looking forward to hearing more about them.
I'm looking forward to hearing more about them, but KOKUNA...
I couldn't make the last recording, so I had to take a break.
I couldn't make it, so I had to take a break.
I hope we can talk a lot at this event.
I hope we can chat a lot.
I'm looking forward to it.
Today, we're going to have a lot of fun with our guests.
We have a lot of plans for you to enjoy together with our guests.
First of all, we have prepared various events for you to enjoy together with the 3 of our favorite culture programs.
First of all, we're going to have a special event for the three of you to talk about your favorite culture programs.
We are going to ask them to talk about their guesses.
Usually, we are on the side of those who are guessed.
But today, I'd like to tell you how wonderful my guesses are.
How confident are you?
Well, it's my first time to give a presentation, so I think it's a special opportunity for me to tell everyone what I like.
I think it's a very special opportunity for me to share what I love.
I would be very happy if you all like it.
Of course I've practiced my presentation.
It's perfect.
I've practiced a lot.
I hope you guys are looking forward to it.
When I asked the staff how much practice they've had.
She looked really nervous.
Please don't say that.
It'll be fine.
I'm sure it's fine.
I'm listening to you perfectly.
Let's go to the first corner.
Okay, Mr. Kokobo, let's hear your title call.
As you may have seen in the broadcast of my guess-telling char.
I'm going to ask you to talk about your own guesses.
This is an event, so I'm not sure if I'm ready to put it on the air yet, but I'm going to do it today in front of our warm family.
But today, in front of our warm family
I hope you will gain a little confidence here.
We hope that you will gain confidence and hopefully lead to future broadcasts.
I hope you will do your best.
Compared to the broadcast, it seems to be a lot easier today.
Compared to the broadcast, yes.
There are a lot of families who have seen the show before, so I'm sure we'll be able to do it safely.
I'm sure we'll be able to do it without any worries.
I don't mean to sound rude when I say practice,
I'd like to have you practice with us.
So, who would like to start first?
Yes, Mr. Akhlaghi.
Let's go to the presentation table.
Okay, let's go.
I'm hearing some warm voices telling me to go for it.
Let's start with the presentation of the theme.
Please do.
Yes, I'm recommending this work.
Yoshie-sanjo
Oh, Yoshie-sanjo!
This is a comic book.
I'd like to ask, "Do any of you know this manga? I mean...
Do any of you know this minor manga? Do any of you know of this minor manga?
No, I don't.
It's a very minor manga work.
You can see it here on Rai Manga.
It's a Korean manga.
But don't worry, it's written in Japanese.
I would like to explain about this manga.
This manga is about...
Yoshie is a high school girl who lives with her father deep in the mountains in the countryside.
This girl on the right
Yoshie transfers to a new school in the city.
And she enters an evil girls' high school where pashiri and bullying are the norm.
It's a new kind of yankee manga!
What a hoo-ha!
She's a high school girl and goes to an all-girls high school.
So Yoshie is actually 21 years old.
Why is a 21 year old attending an all-girls high school?
There's a lot more to the story there, so please take a look.
Please take a look after listening to my presentation.
So, without further ado, let's get started.
First of all, I would like to explain how Ms. Yoshie has influenced me.
I'd like to explain how Mr. Yoshie has influenced me with a diagram.
Here it is.
There it is!
This is my mother's teaching.
Mother's teachings.
My mother taught me...
Think of everyone around you as an enemy.
Yay!
This is a lesson from Cocona's mother.
Oh, yes, my mother's teaching.
I think I've said this a few times on the radio or something.
I've been dancing since I was in elementary school.
The world of dancers is a very tough world.
I used to participate in solo contests.
Solo contests are a battle for each and every dancer.
Everyone is competing to win.
So you shouldn't think that other dancers' dances are good.
I was often told to concentrate only on my own dance.
My mother taught me to think of everyone around me as my enemy.
That's what my mother taught me.
I didn't understand this.
I thought that everything other than dancing was my enemy.
I thought all the kids in my class were my enemies.
At first, I was really gung-ho about it.
But then...
But then I joined an agency called Stardust Promotion.
I joined an agency called Stardust Promotion.
and working as a member of Ebichu
I changed.
I learned the importance of group behavior.
I learned that in elementary school, right?
That's for sure.
I didn't learn it, to be honest.
I don't really think about it.
Your mother was a bit of a rascal, wasn't she?
She was a former gangster.
She's strong.
She's a lot more rounded now.
When you joined Evie, did she tell you how important it was to work as a group?
I learned the importance of working in a group, or rather, the importance of group cooperation and matching up with others, and I think my communication skills also improved there.
Yes!
We are not enemies now, then.
Oh, we are not enemies now.
I just need to turn a corner.
Okay, okay.
I'm sure there's a part of you that's just...
Well, yeah.
Well...
Okay, so...
May I? I met Yoshie-san.
You know how I was affected by this work?
I'd like you to see what I've become.
I'd like you to see what happened to me.
This way, please.
I remember now.
It reminds me of the flower lesson.
It's right, but it's not right.
I don't know if it's okay.
I mean, I could change my mind.
I don't know.
Like this. Like this.
Yeah.
It's a very good thing, don't you think?
No, it's more about the group dynamic.
Yeah, a little bit more, you know, learning.
You mean you're done?
Yeah, I mean, I'm a better rounded person for being in EBITCHU.
I think I've become more rounded.
I think I have learned to cooperate with others.
When I met this Yoshie Sanjo...
I was like, "Oh, my God! I am so happy!
I really don't know what to say.
It reminded me of my ego.
I don't know how to say it.
The first lesson... it came back to me.
The mind yankee part of me came out.
It's a comic that taught me that part of me again.
There is such a part of me...
I also learned about group behavior in Ebitu.
By encountering this manga, I was able to learn about group behavior.
I could think more strongly about how not to be defeated by other members,
I learned how to show myself strongly while learning about group behavior at Yoshie Sanjo.
I learned how to stand up to the rough waves of the world.
You can hone your fighting spirit to face the rough and tumble of the world, can't you?
Have you ever had such an experience?
You laugh bitterly.
But the spirit of defeat and the fighting spirit
The fighting spirit...
I'm sure there are times when it's necessary
It's necessary sometimes.
Is there such a time?
There must be times when you need to be yourself in order to win, right? Is there such a time?
We always endure the bullying of our seniors.
What?
Hey, hey, hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm just kidding.
I said that because we're not on air.
I think there's really a lot to be said for relationships and all that.
If you are wondering how to survive in society, I would like you to read Yoshie-san's book.
That's why.
Next, I would like to tell you the charm of Yoshie-san's book.
Here it is!
Yoshie is just so strong that she beats up a lot of people!
As the name suggests, I really love the way Yoshie is strong and beats up a lot of people, it's really painful and refreshing.
It's really refreshing to watch, isn't it?
Now that I've said that, I'd like to tell you what I like about Yoshie in my own way.
Then, I would like to say what I like about Yoshie.
What is it about Yoshie?
I don't know, she's like, "We're going to fight.
She doesn't have that kind of mindset.
She's always calm.
Always calm.
He's a person who is oriented towards society.
I mean, how should I put it?
The first illustration I saw.
He doesn't look like a yankee.
He has a cool look.
But I transferred to an all-girls high school where bullies and pushers were the worst.
I transferred to an all-girls high school where bullying and paddling were the norm.
So there was a lot of bullying that affected Yoshie too.
So when I beat them up with a single blow
It felt really good.
I really loved it.
I really feel that I'm different from other high school students.
I really love that.
Yes, I do.
So, next.
I'd like to show you my favorite scene.
Next, I'd like to show you my favorite scene.
Oh, here it is.
It's here, and I'd like you to see it here.
There you go.
Oh, this is about page 7, episode 7.
Yes, please look at it and try to see it.
Can you see it?
This is, uh...
It's an empty, abandoned place.
They beat each other with sticks.
Stick-fighting.
But...
And this is the scene where, you know, Yoshie knocks him down with a single blow.
This is the scene.
Here...
Here, this is the enemy called Momoko.
Yoshie's
Enemy
Yes, enemy.
Can you pick up the stick that's fallen down there? First of all
Josie wonders.
You give him the stick.
Thank you.
Boom.
He gets punched in the face. What? Did he hit you?
Are you okay?
Can you see me?
I can see you.
And then Yoshie wobbles.
And then she falls.
Ha-ha-ha! You're so stupid, aren't you? I'm not.
You're good.
Just a ha-ha, right? You were good.
I mean, I can't believe you're the one who stood up to me.
Ha-ha-ha. A million years too early.
Too many teeth? You have a lot of teeth.
I have a lot of teeth, by the way.
Is it that funny?
You're a complete nerd.
Hmm?
Terminal?
You're a terminal patient.
Sta-sta-sta-sta.
I'll prescribe you a special medicine for chuuni-sickness.
Isn't this line so cool already?
Yeah, I don't know.
You can't say that.
Can I borrow that stick?
And I'll lend you this.
Lend me that.
I'm doing the same thing you just did.
Um, we'll give it to each other, the stick.
I see.
You know, the good thing about Yankees is that they're kind, surprisingly.
If they were nice, they wouldn't hit you.
So, I remember, you grab the stick like this, right? And then hit him with a bang,
I only had two teeth.
A lot of teeth were broken.
He hit me.
Oh, here.
I didn't get it.
What do you like about the current scene?
If it's just a fistfight.
I'm tired of watching it.
I don't care who wins.
I don't care who wins, but it's obvious that they're going to win, isn't it?
So, the surrealism of the exchange between the two.
Do you understand?
They give each other things.
But you can feel the kindness of the Yankees.
And the fact that they get hit by one shot is also great.
This was my favorite part.
Their reactions were a bit...
I don't know if I understand it or not.
But I could tell that it's a manga that I'm interested in.
And finally
So, finally, I'd like to demonstrate my favorite scene in the early part of the manga.
I would like to demonstrate my favorite scene in the early part of the manga.
Demonstration? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's going to hit me.
Oh, man, I need a helmet or something.
Thank you very much.
Um, first of all, a correlation and a brief history.
Maybe that you don't know, because we didn't all know.
I'd like to, uh, explain it to you and then demonstrate it.
Yes, sir.
This way.
Well, the main characters of "Yoshie Sanjimatama" are more than that.
There are more and more strong characters.
Well, for now, I'll show you the strong characters here.
Yes, sir.
Yoshie, the main character.
He's the main character.
The main character, Yoshiie, and Momoko.
The people who were passing the stick to each other.
And then there's Hitoshi and Sara.
Sarah is very weak.
She's like a bullied child.
She's a timid girl.
She likes Hitoshi.
She likes Hitoshi because he acts like he's trying to make her think he's the bad guy.
Then he's the worst one.
The worst one.
That's terrible.
The one who needs to be punished the most.
And he's not only that.
He's in a cult religion.
And he's using you to get you to come to his meetings.
Oh, I'm sorry. Make him think I like him.
The bad guy who's trying to bring you in.
But Sara's a little weird.
Like, does she like him?
Like, I don't know. I don't know.
I know, but...
She's trying to recruit people.
Hitoshi gathers people from all over the place.
So we do that.
And Sara wondered how she could do that.
So she lied about being able to eat fried food.
So she gathered about 10 people.
That's amazing.
Fried chicken is very strong.
Karaage is pretty strong in this comic.
I'd go if there was free fried chicken.
Would you go?
I would!
Watch out, watch out!
Don't go, don't go!
Yoshie's invited too.
Yoshie loves fried food.
Yoshie wants fried food, too.
He tried to go, but...
But he couldn't go because he had a part-time job.
He couldn't go.
On the other hand...
Sarah lied about being able to eat fried food.
She got 10 people together.
There's no such thing as fried food.
There isn't.
So when they found out they couldn't eat it, they all went berserk.
Oh, my God!
They were like, "Why isn't there any fried food?
And there was a panic in the hall.
And I don't know what you're talking about.
And then the people who were like, "Why are you rioting?
Hitoshi got angry and beat him up.
Hitoshi was beating him up.
And Momoko, who was there...
She gets beat up again.
Momoko is surprisingly weak.
It says she's so-so.
But Hitoshi is stronger.
He looks strong, but he's weaker.
Hitoshi is even angrier...
Hitoshi got even angrier.
When he was about to punch Hitoshi in the face...
Oh, this is the part where
Yoshie appears.
Yes, sir.
Yoshie's line at that time was so cool that I'd like to demonstrate it.
Let's see...
I will be playing the role of Yoshie.
I'm going to play the role of Yuno-no-Hitoshi and Yuno-no-No-Ga-sara.
So you'll be involved in this?
Yes, sir.
I'm going to open the door with a bang, and you're going to wake me up.
I understand.
I'm used to getting punched in the face.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, on stage.
What's going on? What do you mean?
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, here we go.
Start the music!
Oh, no, he's going over. He's already hitting me. Wow, I'm scared. I don't like it.
I'm here, too, so buy me fried chicken.
So buy me a fried chicken.
That was a really deep bow, and I wanted to do that so bad.
I'm glad you did.
So thank you, both of you.
And thank you all.
Thank you very much.
So we've had a presentation of Yoshie Sanjo.
Once again, please give a big round of applause.
Thank you very much, Mr. Sakuragi.
How was your presentation?
Did you get through to everyone?
My thoughts
You want to see it, don't you?
Personally, I'd like to talk more about it.
But really, Mr. Yoshie, you're so surreal in other ways, too.
It's really a great story to watch when you're feeling stressed out or something.
I hope you all enjoy reading the Line Manga. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's get down to business. Now let's continue. Cocobo, please.
Oh!
Yuno.
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Go for it!
Yes, Yuno has been seriously thinking about how to make us talk about this theme in the culture of the terrestrial wave.
Yes...
I would like to make a presentation with the audience's thoughts as well!
Here is the theme
I want to deliver this to everyone in Yota.
A life with an idol that makes every day fun!
I can hear you all saying, "Oh, this is it!
The theme is right on!
I'm sure all of you here today are a family.
I'm sorry to say this, but you are idol nerds.
We're all friends.
I'm sure you can relate to everything I'm about to say.
And I'd like to bring the parts that got the best reactions to the terrestrial recording, so please clap your hands if you can understand.
If you know what I'm talking about, please clap so loudly that your hands will be torn off!
Quickly, quickly!
In this hall...
Mr. Yamanaka is the only one in the audience who isn't an idol fan.
Mr. Yamanaka is the only one in the audience who's not an idol fan.
That's right.
I don't usually chase after them like you do.
I don't usually follow them like you do.
If there's anything I don't understand or want to ask.
I'll answer all your questions.
I'm sure you'll be able to tell me.
If there's anything you're curious about, you can keep asking.
Thank you very much. I'm not going to tell you my own teaching, but yes, you all teach me. I understand. If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to ask. Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
Yes, well, I don't tell you about Yuno's own teaching,
Anyway, what is Yuno's history as an idol?
In kindergarten, she fell in love with AKB48,
In junior high school, she fell in love with BiSH,
Well, my job doesn't allow me to go to the site very often,
I can't go to the site often because of my work, but I watch their live performances and I'm a pretty normal otaku.
I've come up with my own reasons why I think it's a good idea to promote idols!
Here are some of them
I can work hard every day
Great applause!
I see that everyone else does too.
I'm sure you all have fun things to do almost every day that energize you on a daily basis.
For example, when you win a ticket.
For example, when you win a ticket, you think "I'll do my best until that day's schedule...".
For example, when you win a ticket, you think "I'll do my best until I get the ticket", or "I'll do my best until I get the goods".
For example, when the social networking service of your guess is updated...
You can see your guess's face.
You can see your guess's face on the social networking site.
Or something like that.
I think it's important to update social networking sites at the right time of the day.
I think about the time when people are looking at social networking sites the most and try to update it at that time.
I try to update it at the time when people are looking at social networking sites the most.
That's amazing.
The pressure was incredible!
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm learning from my idols and their guesses.
There's always a favorite idol somewhere. I'm sure there are a lot of idols out there that I don't even know about.
There are... but even these three have their own personalities.
They're probably different types of idols.
I think there are many idols with various personalities.
Each of them has their own good qualities that can't be outdone by others.
They are all different and all good, so you can definitely find your favorite one.
So you can definitely find your favorite idol.
By the way, do you have any particular point that you think makes your idol stand out?
Oh, a certain face?
Then, please shout in unison
Se-no!
We've heard all the transparent faces, but there's one more...
Thank you.
Dance.
The length of your legs.
But you know... each of them has their own reasons.
By the way, what do you like about Yuno's guess?
For example, the way she looks, the way she sings, of course.
the way they dress, the way they take pictures, their sense of style
or his/her own unique sense of style.
I think it's a factor that makes people like them.
For example, his sense of updating social networking sites is also an element that makes me interested in him.
Yes, yes, yes.
For example, the way they update their SNS.
That's true.
I think it's also a sense of style.
I would say that among the three of us, each of us has a different sense of what it means.
Do you have anything that you think you can do better than the two COCONA members?
But COCONA probably.
I think COCONA has a way of making posts on Instagram that can be seen by people overseas.
I think I am very good at SNS, Instagram and TikTok.
I'm good at writing, so I like to write.
I'm good at short sentences.
I think Nonoka is very good at creating blogs that make her fans want to support her even more.
You have a lot of blogs, don't you?
I think her latest blog is the kind of blog that makes people want to be her mother and father.
Thank you very much.
And now, let's see what's next!
Ta-da! Cute gestures!
I'm sure every idol has a very cute gesture.
You know, the ones that come out at the drop of a hat.
As you can see in this situation
The microphone is not on the floor.
or putting it on their feet.
or holding the microphone with both hands...
That kind of thing.
I think that little gestures
I think it's a point that can be pressed.
Well...
Today I'm going to introduce Yuno's favorite idol's gestures.
Yuno's favorite idols.
First of all, Cocona and Nonaka
Cocona and Nonaka's gestures that they think are cute.
May I see them?
Suddenly?
That's sudden.
May I see what you think is cute? What? Sudden? Sudden.
Of course it's sudden.
You mean you think you're doing it?
It's my signature pose.
If I do this, all my fans will like me.
It's like a book.
Okay, I'll do it.
Well, first of all, Coconut, please say hello.
Yes, sir.
Okay, you can just say one word.
I'll start with a gesture.
I'm fine with one word or gesture.
I have a lot of respect for you, Won-yeon.
Won-yeong's hand gesture.
She only uses her middle finger, index finger, and ring finger like this.
This hand gesture is so cute, I'm thinking of doing it someday.
I'm sure everyone here thought it was so cute that it fell out of your voice.
Thank you very much.
Now, may I ask you to join us, Nonoka?
I'll do it.
Yes, I will!
Se-no-Maru!
I knew it!
I saw some cute gestures.
It's good that we can do it together.
But Yuno's cute gestures are totally different
Oh, no...
Is it different?
Yes, that's why I like Cocoa, the idol, except for live performances.
Here's the gesture
She's eating something.
That's amazing.
That's right.
Isn't it a cute gesture when she's eating something?
It's cute.
It's very small animal-like.
It's so cute.
Very cute.
The sight of a girl eating...
I think many of you probably think it's cute.
Yay!
Do you know why?
Is it me?
That was sudden.
I'm usually embarrassed when people see me.
That's what women say.
So it makes you happy to be seen?
No?
But I'm sure you're all right if you feel that way.
Thank you very much.
Well, I don't know if I should say this myself, but...
I'm sure that if Yuno likes something, everyone will like it too.
That's why I decided to make a picture like this for the birthday party.
That's us.
So cute!
Eating and stuff...
Photo 2
Photo 3.
Oh, this is cute.
Thank you.
I've been making pictures of myself eating like this.
I am conscious of it.
I see.
By the way, do you like this picture?
I like it.
I'm glad.
Yes, and I've already finished this non-live section, but I'd like to introduce one more favorite gesture at a live performance.
Yes, the gesture that is not recommended in Ebichu, but you can see it here.
Unrecommended movement? It's not recommended, but it's a gesture that I'd be happy if my guesses did it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Here you go.
It's a very detailed part of A, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
When you put your hands on your hips, not like this, but like this.
Yeah.
This is prettier than this.
Yeah, it's a little more detailed, but...
No, it's not.
It gets hot during the show.
You never let your hair down.
You do let your hair down sometimes.
But then you get hot and you do this.
And when you're doing it like this, you do it like this.
Isn't that what you're supposed to do?
There are 10 of us with the same haircut, so we'll all wear it.
That's true.
So if I do it like this, I'll be in the same room with Maya.
I'll get in trouble with Maya.
We both do it.
Unfortunately, we're not the same.
No?
No.
Oh, I just remembered...
Can we go back to the front of this?
What?
Yes.
Well, that's messy.
Well, I guess I'm not going to do it then.
Free, free, free.
Can I have your answer?
Here is the answer.
I really like the gesture of touching the earpiece, although it is not recommended in janjan ebichu.
Oh! You like it?
Well, there are some idols who take their earphones off to listen to their fans' calls, for example.
Oh, sure, sure. As a viewer, I've always admired air monitors and thought they were cool and cute.
But it's something that only very advanced people do.
That's right.
By taking off one ear, the sound outside is different from what you hear in your ear.
In Yuno's case, it would make her dance really off.
You mean during the performance?
That's difficult.
It's difficult, but I'm sure there are people who would like it.
Yes, I do.
Well, you know, it's not a good idea because it worries the sound engineer.
But as long as you're pushing it, it's really cute.
But as long as they're pushing, they're really cute, and it doesn't matter what they're doing, they're cute.
But in the end... in the end... in the end... in the end... when all is said and done... you are cute no matter what you do...
That's right.
I hope I've conveyed to you how wonderful life is pushing idols.
I hope you got the message that Yuno thinks it's a wonderful life to be an idol auce.
Oh, I'm glad.
Thank you very much.
I would like you to know that idols are working on even the smallest details such as fingertips and hand shapes,
Thank you very much, and please give a big round of applause.
Now, Ms. Kazami.
Thank you very much.
Please give a big round of applause.
Okay, please.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
Your voice is so quiet. Hey! You're so quiet.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, oh, oh!
Well, no, no, this is an event hall.
I have to present my pitch here today.
I wonder if I'll be able to do it well?
I'm worried about the other members, they're all so weird.
Weird.
What's wrong?
Well, well, well. I guess that's just how it starts.
Um, so...
What I, Noika Kazami, would like to present is...
This way.
A drifter!
Oh, no, that's nice.
Yes, it's good
Well... some of the family members...
Some of our family members know that I'm a fan of Drifting.
By the way, this is a picture of me performing at my first birthday party.
I showed this picture at my first birthday party.
This is a picture of the parody of the Sumo tournament I performed at the first birthday party.
Once again, let me explain Drifting.
It stands for "The Drifters".
It is a music band and a comedy group formed in 1956.
Led by Chosuke Ikariya
The Drifters were a five-member group led by Chosuke Ikariya and consisting of Tea Kato, Koji Nakamoto, Boo Takagi, and Ken Shimura.
Drifting Big Bang" and "All together at 8 o'clock" were broadcast on TV in the Showa Era (1926-1989).
8 o'clock show was very popular among children in those days.
The highest rating was 50.5%, making it a national TV program.
That's amazing, isn't it?
It was so popular.
For those of you who are in your 40s now.
I'm sure you must have rubbed your sleepy eyes on Saturday nights
Rubbing their sleepy eyes on Saturday nights.
I wasn't born there.
My mom and dad loved it.
That's why I watched the DVDs.
I've seen all the Drift movies at the local video store.
Yes, that's right... that's how much I love this masterpiece... the Drift.
I'm sure you all understand the appeal of Drifting, so today, I've prepared this theme for you.
What's up?
I'm sure you know what I'm talking about.
I want to refer to it.
Drifting ism!
Yay!
Yes, sir.
First of all...
You know...
Entertainment
Textbook
From the drifting
I'd like to make a suggestion.
I would like to make a suggestion.
First of all
I found something in drifting that is not in ebichu.
I'd like to propose something that I've found in drifting but not in shrimping.
I found something that is in Drift but not in Ebichu.
I would like to announce it.
Here it is!
Ois.
Ois?
There's no Ois.
No Oyce?
Yes, Ois, let me explain.
The leader of the group, Mr. Chousuke Ikaria.
It's a greeting when the leader, Mr. Chousuke Ikaria, appears on stage.
The first one is the one I used to do.
I used to say "Ois" at the beginning.
I was the first one to say "Oisu".
To be precise, there are no "Ois" people in Ebichu.
I am talking about Mr. Chowske Ikariya, of course.
To put it more simply, this is what I mean.
There is no one who is in charge in Ebichu.
Especially the younger members are not in charge.
Recently... as we saw yesterday...
Even the MCs have weird pauses, like what are you going to say?
There are strange pauses.
You're feeling it, aren't you?
Yes, we're thinking about the topic.
Before the show, we'll talk about this kind of thing.
And then sometimes they just fly by and fly by and fly by and fly by and fly by.
Yes, that's right.
Well, I mean, there's usually no one who's an Ois.
When I gave them an oyster earlier, both of them looked at me with a blank stare.
In the case of the riffs, after the oice, one by one, they come out and say strange things.
I want to bring that kind of thing to EBITTU.
Yes, that's necessary.
Okay, let's try it once.
Quick, quick, quick!
When I give the signal, you two...
Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're in.
Come in as a weird character.
I'm going to have to ask you to throw up.
Can I ask you to come in as a weird character?
Weird character?
No, I don't want to.
No, no, no, no.
What kind of theme?
Anything.
Let's go with a theme like the Ebitu family.
And...
What?
Like the EBITCHU family. Like that family.
Oh...
Let's make it something like... the eldest daughter and the youngest daughter.
Let's try it.
Okay, everyone.
Hey!
One more time!
Okay...
My eldest and youngest are coming home today.
What's he doing already? He's late.
Hey! Come on! Eldest daughter!
Wait a minute.
You know, first of all, I told them to come in one at a time.
You know, you didn't listen.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let's start over.
Come on in, eldest.
Oh, Grandpa's coming in.
It's not grandpa. It's the dog.
A dog.
What's with the dog all of a sudden? You don't look that much like a dog.
Meow.
That doesn't mean I don't like cats, spider.
What's the matter with you? I'm getting angry, aren't I?
Okay, next. Eldest.
Oh.
What's that?
Oh, dear.
She's a grandmother.
You're the eldest and she's your grandmother?
I'm not the eldest.
What's that? You're scaring me.
I said, "I'm scared.
Grandma's gonna fly us out of here.
You're scaring me, Grandma.
Grandma, you're like Yoshie... you're like Yoshie.
Grandma used to be...
Grandma, you've got the Yoshie-isms.
I used to be Yoshie.
Don't get stuck.
Thank you, both of you.
Thank you very much.
I'm afraid we're running a little late.
Can I ask you a few questions?
First of all, we've come up with a live performance for the EbiChu concert.
Look at this.
Look at that!
A live performance that destroys the set!
Oh, no!
Oh my God!
They do that in drifting too... where the whole house is destroyed.
Why don't you do the same thing with the shrimp stew?
Here's what happened.
At the end of the show, the house is destroyed.
And for encore, they dance on the broken set.
I think this is a good idea, and we'll continue to do it.
I'd like to bring in a live performance of falling down the stairs.
I made up a solo song.
When he sings his solo song, everyone sings it.
All the members
After the solo song, they all play the khoroge.
Sounds like fun.
Yeah.
For example...
Oh, like, "Oh, my God, this is Yoo's...
Yuni's finished singing.
Yeah.
Finished singing.
Ah!
Ta-da!
Rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble, rumble... Yu's song is over.
Rumble-rumble-rumble...
Isn't it good?
So many moves!
Go on, go on, go on.
Interesting.
Spaceship Live
This might be the most decent thing I've ever seen.
This is Chiyo Kato and Ken Shimura.
It's a comedy, but the songs during the day are often ballads...
Oh! If you all watch it, you'll see them singing weightless, right?
No, no, the guy next to me looks like he's in bad shape.
I know it's hard, but if you have trouble seeing the audience, please stand on your head.
I'd like you to stand on your head and look at them.
Standing on your head.
If you stand on your head like this, it will be a very interesting show.
I think you can see a new way
I think you can see a new way.
I hope you could understand the charm of the live show filled with my favorite drifters and drifterism.
I hope you could understand the charm of the live show filled with my favorite drifting and drifting-isms.
Thank you very much for your presentation.
Thank you very much! I wish I could have listened to more!
I wish I could have listened to more!
You all have your own passion for what you love.
Now then, let's go to another project.
Let's go to the other project.
It's getting kind of late.
Next title...
Kasami-san, may I ask you to do it?
Okay, I'll go.
What's your favorite Ebichu song to listen to in the summer?
So now we're going to ask the audience to tell us what song they'd like to hear in the summer.
We're going to ask the audience to tell us their favorite song of the summer.
We will ask the audience to fill out the Googogle form in advance.
We've asked each and every one of you to tell us your favorite song of the summer, and we're going to put it in the drawing box that will come out now.
We will put them in the lottery box that will appear in the hall.
In terms of the number of songs, how many Ebichu songs do you have in total?
We have nearly 200 songs, and I think it's more than that!
Did each of you write down the songs you would like to hear in the summer in that list?
Thank you.
I'm not just going to ask you to tell me this.
I've asked the three members to make bingo cards in advance
I've asked the three members to make bingo cards in advance to predict the summer songs that the audience might guess.
So, we're going to draw lots now.
The member who completes the bingo card first wins.
There may not be enough time to complete the bingo.
Let's go as long as we have time.
In other words, the fans guess which song you are playing.
This is a project to see if our hearts can communicate with each other.
How confident are you?
Well, well, we always communicate with each other, don't we?
Well, we always communicate with each other, don't we?
How's it going? We're good.
Let's see what kind of bingo cards the three of you wrote.
We've set up the camera now, so you can see it before the show.
Like this.
They're all over the place.
It's all over the place.
How do you feel about each other's bingo cards?
How confident are you?
I'd say it's a love card.
I knew it would be popular.
I wanted to be in it, too.
But you know what?
It all seems to be there.
Everyone seems to like it.
Yeah, I like them all.
If there's a bingo at the end, and there's a bingo at the end...
The person who draws the last one...
If you're a guest, we'll give a prize to the person who draws the last card.
We'll also have a special gift for you.
So please come and join us and see if you can get your own bingo card.
Let's get started.
Let's draw lots.
Who'd like to go first?
Coconner.
Okay, I'll draw first.
That's him.
Here you go.
Mother Tontons Turbo.
Go, go, here we go, Rockley.
Lockley. - Oh, my God, he's not in.
Oh my god, here we go!
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
I'll see you later.
Thank you very much.
But you can put it in.
Did you have a hard time deciding whether to write it or not?
Yes, it was a tough decision.
We performed it yesterday.
Yes, we did.
Shall we go on and on?
That's it right there.
Shall we leave it here?
Yes, sir.
Anything you want to say?
Here we go.
Yes, sir.
Don!
Mr. Masaki, mission survivor!
Ah!
Summer means Famien!
If you're going to take on water, it's called Water Survivor.
Yay!
Ah, it went!
Already reaching!
Too early! So fast!
Next, I'm going to play "NONO".
Then I'll continue and draw.
Then...
Coco!
Lovely smiley baby!
Then, Yunonoka gets one point each.
Yes!
When the name of the song comes out...
When the name of the song comes out, the audience shouts "Oh, wow!
Love Smile is really good, isn't it?
Okay, let's go!
Misaki-san! Thank you so much!
I'll go to the next song...
I want to seduce you, Takoyaki-san! This way!
Double reach, so it's like triple reach.
That's right.
We do this every year, don't we?
Then, let's continue.
Well then, here we go!
Mr. Mogu, 23rd Summer Night!
What?
Here it is!
It's a bingo! Congratulations! Don't make me say any more... but I can't stop thinking about it...
You're early.
Well, I just played it and got a bingo.
What's your nickname again?
Is Mr. Mogu here?
I've got a big prize for you, Mr. Mog.
Hello, Mr. Mog?
Hello, Mr. Mog... Ah! There he is!
May I ask you to come to the front, please?
I'll give you your present, and then...
Congratulations.
Ms. Kazami has something for you.
What's the present?
The present is... ta-da!
We've made it even though we haven't made one for the staff yet!
It's not a "Guess Culture Staff Jumper" but a "Guess Culture Viewer Jumper".
It's a very rare item that will only be available once in this world!
I think it's funny that it says "viewer" on it.
It's not a staff jumper, but a viewer's jumper.
It's a very rare item, isn't it?
I'll sign it, right?
Okay, I'll give it to you directly.
You want me to give it to him?
Let's give it to him.
Okay, I'll hold on to it.
Homey.
Yes, sir.
Sorry about the mess.
Congratulations on your bingo.
Congratulations.
Please give a big round of applause.
And that's that.
I'm sorry to say that the time has already run out.
I'm sorry to say that the time has already run out, and we've come to the end.
I know it's a short time, but could you give us your impressions
Could you tell us your impressions one by one?
Yes, I think so.
I think each one of us gave a different and passionate presentation.
The bingo at the end was a rush.
I was really happy to be a part of such a fun event.
Thank you so much to everyone who came!
Thank you very much!
And from Ms. Kunitomo...
Yes, that's right.
I'm sure each and every one of you has a lot to say about your presentation.
I'm sure there were still many things to be said.
I think there were a lot of things I haven't talked about yet.
I would like to do it again, and it was a lot of fun.
If you have a chance to come again, I would be very happy if you could all come.
Thank you very much.
Yes, Mr. Azami.
Yes, this is the Chayamachi guess festival this time.
I got to know other people's guesses, and
I was also able to talk about my own guesses.
And this program called "Mystery Culture" is also a great opportunity for me to talk about my own guesses.
I am still talking about many more guesses.
I hope you will enjoy the show as well!
Thank you very much.
Yes, there are three of us on the show, and we'll be talking about our guesses.
The next broadcast will be on June 25th.
In this episode, you will be able to see what the three of us did on location at today's Guess Fest, so please be sure to tune in and watch.
What do you think of the three's presentations that may be connected to the broadcast someday?
I would have liked to hear more about the one in the "a," but it was chaotic.
I'm looking forward to seeing it in the future.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's have the Ebituyu members close the show.
Mr. Sakuragi, please.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Dismissed.
Thank you very much for dismissing Thank you very much for dismissing
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
by H..